tiger.do 2019-05-26

# tiger.do Privacy Policy

  * At Tiger Digitech Private Limited, we recognize that privacy is important. The Policy applies to the Services mentioned in the Terms of Use. Tiger Digitech Private Limited is an web technology based online service that enables website owners to engage with visitors & identify prospective business leads. The administrative user interface (UI) is a mobile application, and the visitor UI is a website chat plugin.  

  * Information we collect and how we use it:  

  * Personally identifiable information collected through the use of the Tiger Digitech Private Limited service: 
  * Website owner - Information such as Name, Email address & Website Domain name is collected at the time of registration and used within the system for identification & communication purposes. Additionally, while configuring chat settings with other user information such as your chat name & display image, information as submitted will also be uploaded to our servers and displayed to your website visitors. 
  * Support team - Information of team members is collected from the website owner when adding new team members. This information is and used within the system for identification & communication purposes. Additionally, while configuring chat settings with other user information such as team member chat name & display image, information as submitted will also be uploaded to our servers and displayed to your website visitors. 
  * Website visitors - Website visitors are tracked using web service requests, browser cookies & IP address for the purpose of uniquely identifying visitors, their website behaviour & their likely location to the website owner and support team members. Additionally, the visitor may voluntarily provide contact information using the [offline/away] form, or as per the lead form configured by the website owner. This information with chat histories is available to the website owner & support team members to view within the Tiger Digitech Private Limited app, or download for offline processing. 
  * Other information collected: 
  * When you & your team uses Tiger Digitech Private Limited services, our servers automatically record information that your app sends whenever you use it. These server logs may include information such as your web service requests, IP address, operating system, date & time of your request and one or more identifiers that may uniquely identify your device. 
  * When your website visitor visits your website which loads the Tiger Digitech Private Limited plugin, our servers automatically record information that your visitor's browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as web service requests, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your visitor's browser/computer/mobile/other device. 
  * Tiger Digitech Private Limited collects the above information, which include the sensitive personal data or information, from the users of this site for providing the Services to users and other purpose as mentioned in the Terms of Use. In addition to the above, such purposes include: 
  * Display of the content for advertising; 
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services; 
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; 
  * Developing new services; and 
  * Offering new services. 
  * The information collected shall be used for the purpose for which it has been collected. 
  * Tiger Digitech Private Limited will not retain that the information for longer than is required for the purposes for which the information may lawfully be used or is otherwise required under the Terms of Use or any other law for the time being in force. 
  * Other sites: This Privacy Policy applies to the Tiger Digitech Private Limited service. We do not exercise control over the websites which use the Tiger Digitech Private Limited plugin, the sites links provided by website owners and their support team members using our service. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 
  * Choices for personal information: 
  * When you register, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 
  * If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 
  * You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Tiger Digitech Private Limited may not be able to provide some or all part of the service to you. 
  * Information sharing: 
  * We require your opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 
  * We provide the information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy. 
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Tiger Digitech Private Limited, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 
  * If Tiger Digitech Private Limited becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide intimate you before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. 
  * We may disclose the sensitive personal data or information: 
  * to any person, if such disclose is required for a lawful purpose connected with a function or activity of Tiger Digitech Private Limited. 
  * where the disclosure is necessary for compliance of a legal obligation. 

  * We have to disclose the sensitive personal data or information with Government agencies mandated under the law to obtain information for the purpose of verification of identity, or for prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, prosecution, and punishment of offences. 
  * Tiger Digitech Private Limited shall publish your information onto the Site according to your profile settings. 
  * Information security: 
  * We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 
  * We restrict access to personal information to Tiger Digitech Private Limited's employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 
  * Data integrity: 

Tiger Digitech Private Limited processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

Accessing and updating personal information: 

When you use Tiger Digitech Private Limited services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users' personal information. We provide the details for these procedures in the specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services. 

Enforcement: 

Tiger Digitech Private Limited regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or Tiger Digitech Private Limited's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at support@tiger.do 

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is Tiger Digitech Private Limited's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Tiger Digitech Private Limited and an individual. 

  * Changes in this policy: 
  * Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior version of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. 
  * If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through the app or at support@tiger.do
